http://www.teampromark.com/privacy-notice

Shopping cart
(0)
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Register
Log in
Wishlist
(0)
NFL Super Bowl
Super Bowl LIV Champions - Kansas City Chiefs (2019-20)
Back
Super Bowl LIV Champions - Kansas City Chiefs (2019-20)
Privacy Notice
Introduction to Policy. In this Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy"), the terms "you", "your" and "Customer" refer to all visitors to the Sports Licensing Solutions website who set up an account (whether a purchase has been made or not) or otherwise use the website. "We" and "our" refer to Sports Licensing Solutions LLC. "Website" refers to www.fanmats.com.
Introduction to Sports Licensing Solutions LLC. We are a provider of mats (the "Products") and provider of reseller programs to further sell and distribute the Products (the "Services").
Information Collected. We receive and store any information you enter on our Website or give us in any other way; for example, the details of your shipping and billing contacts, including names, addresses, telephone numbers and e-mail addresses, and your credit card or banking information (collectively the "Information").
Use of Information. We will use the Information for fulfilment of the Products and to provide the Services. We will use your Information to bill you properly, administer your account, ship the Products, and properly perform the Services. We may also use the Information to communicate with you; for example, to notify you about upcoming developments or news and/or important notices or promotions affecting the Products and Services by way of e-mail. We will take reasonable precautions including use of Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software to encrypt sensitive financial information (for example, credit card numbers or banking information) or security information.
Sharing of Information with Other Parties. We will not sell, share, rent or disclose in any form personal information from Customers for commercial purposes. We may share certain Information with those who are responsible for handling your account or performing other necessary services that you require. Although we may share sensitive financial information (for example, credit card numbers or banking information) or security information with such parties where necessary and appropriate, we will not share such information with other third parties; except that we may disclose Information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce or apply the conditions of use of this Website, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of us, our users, or others. This may include exchanging Information with other organizations for protection against fraud and reduction of credit risk. We may aggregate information from Customers (for example, to determine trends and visitor needs) and may present to others some aggregated information that is in no way individually identifiable.
Your Consent. By ordering the Products, applying for or using the Services or by applying for an account you acknowledge that you have read and agree to be bound by all terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. By submitting your information to us, you evidence your consent to our storing and using the personal information submitted as indicated in this Privacy Policy.
Your Responsibility. Username and password information is e-mailed to you for your record. It is your responsibility to protect against unauthorized use or access to your username and password and to your computer.
Modifications to Policy. We, in our sole discretion, may modify the Privacy Policy from time to time. Please check this page periodically for changes. If you disagree with any of the changes to our Privacy Policy, please do not continue to use the Website. You may also contact us and cancel your account.
Cookies. We may use cookie files to make it easier to for users to access our Website and Services. A cookie is stored on your hard-drive and can contain information, although the only personal information a cookie may contain is information that you yourself provide. A cookie cannot read data from your hard-drive.
Contacting Us. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, our website practices, or your personal experience dealing with this web site, you can contact our offices at customerservice@fanmats.com.
Sports Licensing Solutions, LLC is registered with the Fair Labor Association as a Category C collegiate licensee and is committed to upholding the FLA Workplace Code of Conduct in facilities producing its collegiate products.
Contact
+1-800-525-5923
customerservice@fanmats.com
Join Our Mailing List
Sign up for our newsletter
Wait...
Copyright © 2020 Fanmats. All rights reserved.
This website uses cookies. By using this website you consent to the use of cookies.
